Student Newspapers; Collection ua809
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Albany Student Press Website, 2013 February 15 - 2017 June 1; 11; 326 captures
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press | UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 December 9
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 December 16
    crawl: 187761
    start_date: 2015-12-16T13:56:25Z
    original_start_date: 2015-12-16T13:56:25Z
    processing_end_date: 2015-12-19T01:29:30Z
    end_date: 2015-12-19T01:13:48Z
    elapsed_ms: 213435183
    discovered_count: 155375
    novel_count: 134793
    duplicate_count: 20582
    downloaded_count: 155375
    warc_revisit_count: 20577
    warc_url_count: 155330
    total_data_in_kbs: 5626191
    duplicate_bytes: 1142777574
    warc_compressed_bytes: 370122515
    doc_rate: 0.73
    kb_rate: 26.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 December 16
  - Albany Student Press UAlbanys independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 December 20
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 December 23
    crawl: 188654
    start_date: 2015-12-23T13:56:25Z
    original_start_date: 2015-12-23T13:56:25Z
    processing_end_date: 2015-12-26T03:45:41Z
    end_date: 2015-12-26T03:31:16Z
    elapsed_ms: 221686224
    discovered_count: 229477
    novel_count: 204090
    duplicate_count: 25387
    downloaded_count: 229477
    warc_revisit_count: 25385
    warc_url_count: 229436
    total_data_in_kbs: 6017020
    duplicate_bytes: 1233705299
    warc_compressed_bytes: 636462150
    doc_rate: 1.04
    kb_rate: 27.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 December 23
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 December 30
    crawl: 189431
    start_date: 2015-12-30T13:56:23Z
    original_start_date: 2015-12-30T13:56:23Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-01-01T22:53:33Z
    end_date: 2016-01-01T22:39:36Z
    elapsed_ms: 204186366
    discovered_count: 157196
    novel_count: 134500
    duplicate_count: 22696
    downloaded_count: 157196
    warc_revisit_count: 22695
    warc_url_count: 157153
    total_data_in_kbs: 5609238
    duplicate_bytes: 1186822666
    warc_compressed_bytes: 1330877084
    doc_rate: 0.77
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2015 December 30
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 January 6
    crawl: 190279
    start_date: 2016-01-06T13:56:28Z
    original_start_date: 2016-01-06T13:56:28Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-01-09T03:56:05Z
    end_date: 2016-01-09T03:44:07Z
    elapsed_ms: 222443303
    discovered_count: 157037
    novel_count: 136042
    duplicate_count: 20995
    downloaded_count: 157037
    warc_revisit_count: 20995
    warc_url_count: 156997
    total_data_in_kbs: 5626363
    duplicate_bytes: 1148586387
    warc_compressed_bytes: 1358661126
    doc_rate: 0.71
    kb_rate: 25.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 January 6
  - Albany Student Press UAlbanys independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 January 12
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 January 13
    crawl: 191380
    start_date: 2016-01-13T13:56:32Z
    original_start_date: 2016-01-13T13:56:32Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-01-16T05:54:26Z
    end_date: 2016-01-16T05:41:12Z
    elapsed_ms: 229475924
    discovered_count: 158327
    novel_count: 135681
    duplicate_count: 22646
    downloaded_count: 158327
    warc_revisit_count: 22643
    warc_url_count: 158279
    total_data_in_kbs: 5685088
    duplicate_bytes: 1188103055
    warc_compressed_bytes: 353984746
    doc_rate: 0.69
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 January 13
  - Albany Student Press UAlbanys independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 January 15
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 January 20
    crawl: 192263
    start_date: 2016-01-20T13:56:36Z
    original_start_date: 2016-01-20T13:56:36Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-01-23T06:23:01Z
    end_date: 2016-01-23T06:06:01Z
    elapsed_ms: 230953044
    discovered_count: 246001
    novel_count: 219799
    duplicate_count: 26202
    downloaded_count: 246001
    warc_revisit_count: 26202
    warc_url_count: 245949
    total_data_in_kbs: 6713557
    duplicate_bytes: 1213821242
    warc_compressed_bytes: 1839707208
    kb_rate: 29.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 January 20
  - Albany Student Press UAlbanys independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 January 25
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 January 27
    crawl: 193265
    start_date: 2016-01-27T13:56:25Z
    original_start_date: 2016-01-27T13:56:25Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-01-30T06:19:25Z
    end_date: 2016-01-30T05:57:34Z
    elapsed_ms: 230459799
    discovered_count: 247497
    novel_count: 221427
    duplicate_count: 26070
    downloaded_count: 247497
    warc_revisit_count: 26069
    warc_url_count: 247441
    total_data_in_kbs: 6935344
    duplicate_bytes: 1200049437
    warc_compressed_bytes: 918900945
    kb_rate: 30.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 January 27
  - Albany Student Press UAlbanys independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 January 31
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 February 3
    crawl: 194353
    start_date: 2016-02-11T15:27:29Z
    original_start_date: 2016-02-03T13:56:24Z
    last_resumption: 1397
    processing_end_date: 2016-02-12T02:29:01Z
    end_date: 2016-02-12T02:20:59Z
    elapsed_ms: 298129292
    time_limit: 302412
    discovered_count: 173887
    novel_count: 159914
    duplicate_count: 13973
    resumption_count: 1
    downloaded_count: 173887
    warc_revisit_count: 13972
    warc_url_count: 173854
    total_data_in_kbs: 9097021
    duplicate_bytes: 1090946294
    warc_compressed_bytes: 21922924
    doc_rate: 0.58
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 February 3
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 February 10
    crawl: 195486
    start_date: 2016-02-10T13:56:41Z
    original_start_date: 2016-02-10T13:56:41Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-02-11T20:22:00Z
    end_date: 2016-02-11T19:52:27Z
    elapsed_ms: 107737266
    discovered_count: 108373
    novel_count: 98612
    duplicate_count: 9761
    downloaded_count: 108373
    download_failures: 0
    warc_revisit_count: 9761
    warc_url_count: 108365
    total_data_in_kbs: 5855329
    duplicate_bytes: 763875937
    warc_compressed_bytes: 1617179670
    doc_rate: 1.01
    kb_rate: 54.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 February 10
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 February 17
    crawl: 196660
    Crawl Rules
    start_date: 2016-02-17T13:56:32Z
    original_start_date: 2016-02-17T13:56:32Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-02-17T14:11:35Z
    end_date: 2016-02-17T14:03:32Z
    elapsed_ms: 409834
    document_limit: 1000
    status: FINISHED_DOCUMENT_LIMIT
    discovered_count: 3612
    novel_count: 603
    duplicate_count: 404
    queued_count: 2605
    downloaded_count: 1007
    warc_revisit_count: 404
    warc_url_count: 1002
    total_data_in_kbs: 80078
    duplicate_bytes: 17198554
    warc_compressed_bytes: 11028838
    doc_rate: 2.46
    kb_rate: 195.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 February 17
  - Albany Student Press UAlbanys independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 February 21
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 February 24
    crawl: 197838
    start_date: 2016-02-24T17:10:02Z
    original_start_date: 2016-02-24T13:56:35Z
    last_resumption: 1412
    processing_end_date: 2016-02-24T17:28:43Z
    end_date: 2016-02-24T17:20:17Z
    elapsed_ms: 909014
    document_limit: 2000
    discovered_count: 5009
    novel_count: 1513
    duplicate_count: 494
    queued_count: 3002
    downloaded_count: 2007
    warc_revisit_count: 494
    warc_url_count: 2002
    total_data_in_kbs: 148593
    duplicate_bytes: 23191807
    warc_compressed_bytes: 19593087
    doc_rate: 2.21
    kb_rate: 163.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 February 24
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 March 2
    crawl: 199042
    start_date: 2016-03-02T13:56:26Z
    original_start_date: 2016-03-02T13:56:26Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-03-02T14:06:54Z
    end_date: 2016-03-02T13:58:47Z
    elapsed_ms: 132306
    discovered_count: 3878
    novel_count: 632
    duplicate_count: 414
    queued_count: 2832
    downloaded_count: 1046
    warc_revisit_count: 414
    warc_url_count: 1038
    total_data_in_kbs: 55940
    duplicate_bytes: 19326033
    warc_compressed_bytes: 14345537
    doc_rate: 7.91
    kb_rate: 422.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 March 2
  - Albany Student Press UAlbanys independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 March 5
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 March 9
    crawl: 200504
    start_date: 2016-03-09T13:57:42Z
    original_start_date: 2016-03-09T13:57:42Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-03-09T14:09:46Z
    end_date: 2016-03-09T14:00:54Z
    elapsed_ms: 175774
    discovered_count: 2957
    novel_count: 671
    duplicate_count: 343
    queued_count: 1943
    downloaded_count: 1014
    download_failures: 1
    warc_revisit_count: 343
    warc_url_count: 997
    total_data_in_kbs: 44382
    duplicate_bytes: 8845100
    warc_compressed_bytes: 9371982
    doc_rate: 5.77
    kb_rate: 252.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 March 9
  - Albany Student Press UAlbanys independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 March 15
  - Albany Student Press UAlbanys independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 March 16
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 March 16
    crawl: 201649
    start_date: 2016-03-16T13:56:39Z
    original_start_date: 2016-03-16T13:56:39Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-03-16T19:15:09Z
    end_date: 2016-03-16T14:02:18Z
    elapsed_ms: 331489
    discovered_count: 3018
    novel_count: 637
    duplicate_count: 364
    queued_count: 2017
    downloaded_count: 1001
    warc_revisit_count: 363
    warc_url_count: 984
    total_data_in_kbs: 51425
    duplicate_bytes: 9746104
    warc_compressed_bytes: 10164854
    doc_rate: 3.02
    kb_rate: 155.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 March 16
  - Albany Student Press UAlbanys independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 March 21
  - Albany Student Press UAlbanys independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 March 23
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 March 23
    crawl: 202808
    start_date: 2016-03-23T13:56:23Z
    original_start_date: 2016-03-23T13:56:23Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-03-23T14:07:34Z
    end_date: 2016-03-23T13:59:01Z
    elapsed_ms: 145811
    discovered_count: 3751
    novel_count: 601
    duplicate_count: 424
    queued_count: 2726
    downloaded_count: 1025
    warc_revisit_count: 424
    warc_url_count: 1019
    total_data_in_kbs: 54553
    duplicate_bytes: 13806925
    warc_compressed_bytes: 22651270
    doc_rate: 7.03
    kb_rate: 374.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 March 23
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 March 23
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 March 23
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 March 30
    crawl: 204479
    start_date: 2016-03-30T13:56:28Z
    original_start_date: 2016-03-30T13:56:28Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-03-30T14:13:29Z
    end_date: 2016-03-30T14:03:34Z
    elapsed_ms: 407143
    discovered_count: 3856
    novel_count: 490
    duplicate_count: 519
    queued_count: 2847
    downloaded_count: 1009
    warc_revisit_count: 518
    warc_url_count: 1006
    total_data_in_kbs: 48473
    duplicate_bytes: 18398080
    warc_compressed_bytes: 9841899
    doc_rate: 2.48
    kb_rate: 119.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 March 30
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 March 30
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 March 30
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 April 6
    crawl: 205727
    start_date: 2016-04-06T13:56:28Z
    original_start_date: 2016-04-06T13:56:28Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-04-06T14:12:22Z
    end_date: 2016-04-06T14:00:19Z
    elapsed_ms: 222407
    discovered_count: 3782
    novel_count: 527
    duplicate_count: 481
    queued_count: 2774
    downloaded_count: 1008
    warc_revisit_count: 481
    warc_url_count: 991
    total_data_in_kbs: 51744
    duplicate_bytes: 19819051
    warc_compressed_bytes: 10124379
    doc_rate: 4.53
    kb_rate: 232.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 April 6
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 April 6
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 April 6
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 April 13
    crawl: 207126
    start_date: 2016-04-13T13:57:12Z
    original_start_date: 2016-04-13T13:57:12Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-04-13T14:35:45Z
    end_date: 2016-04-13T14:11:25Z
    elapsed_ms: 730570
    discovered_count: 3717
    novel_count: 543
    duplicate_count: 467
    queued_count: 2707
    downloaded_count: 1010
    warc_revisit_count: 467
    warc_url_count: 993
    total_data_in_kbs: 47679
    duplicate_bytes: 19867311
    warc_compressed_bytes: 8984343
    doc_rate: 1.38
    kb_rate: 65.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 April 13
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 April 13
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 April 13
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 April 20
    crawl: 208249
    start_date: 2016-04-20T13:56:30Z
    original_start_date: 2016-04-20T13:56:30Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-04-20T14:35:46Z
    end_date: 2016-04-20T14:06:26Z
    elapsed_ms: 585888
    discovered_count: 3768
    duplicate_count: 345
    queued_count: 2752
    downloaded_count: 1016
    warc_revisit_count: 345
    warc_url_count: 998
    total_data_in_kbs: 45659
    duplicate_bytes: 10194689
    warc_compressed_bytes: 10294578
    doc_rate: 1.73
    kb_rate: 77.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 April 20
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 April 20
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 April 20
  - Albany Student Press UAlbanys independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 April 25
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 April 27
    crawl: 209496
    start_date: 2016-04-27T13:56:29Z
    original_start_date: 2016-04-27T13:56:29Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-04-27T23:20:10Z
    end_date: 2016-04-27T23:09:41Z
    elapsed_ms: 153883
    discovered_count: 3811
    duplicate_count: 489
    queued_count: 2795
    warc_revisit_count: 489
    total_data_in_kbs: 48524
    duplicate_bytes: 19325301
    warc_compressed_bytes: 9342547
    doc_rate: 6.6
    kb_rate: 315.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 April 27
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 April 27
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 April 27
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 May 4
    crawl: 210614
    start_date: 2016-05-04T13:56:31Z
    original_start_date: 2016-05-04T13:56:31Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-05-04T14:08:03Z
    end_date: 2016-05-04T13:59:21Z
    elapsed_ms: 155660
    discovered_count: 3775
    novel_count: 537
    duplicate_count: 468
    queued_count: 2770
    downloaded_count: 1005
    warc_revisit_count: 468
    warc_url_count: 995
    total_data_in_kbs: 56629
    duplicate_bytes: 16389609
    warc_compressed_bytes: 13561162
    doc_rate: 6.46
    kb_rate: 363.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 May 4
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 May 4
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 May 4
  - Albany Student Press UAlbanys independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 May 8
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 May 11
    crawl: 211781
    start_date: 2016-05-11T13:56:26Z
    original_start_date: 2016-05-11T13:56:26Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-05-11T14:07:20Z
    end_date: 2016-05-11T13:58:56Z
    elapsed_ms: 140633
    discovered_count: 3783
    duplicate_count: 483
    queued_count: 2773
    warc_revisit_count: 483
    total_data_in_kbs: 50397
    duplicate_bytes: 16902247
    warc_compressed_bytes: 7438596
    doc_rate: 7.18
    kb_rate: 358.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 May 11
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 May 11
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 May 11
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 May 18
    crawl: 213109
    start_date: 2016-05-18T13:56:29Z
    original_start_date: 2016-05-18T13:56:29Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-05-18T14:07:23Z
    end_date: 2016-05-18T13:59:09Z
    elapsed_ms: 146982
    discovered_count: 3029
    novel_count: 719
    duplicate_count: 290
    queued_count: 2020
    warc_revisit_count: 290
    warc_url_count: 999
    total_data_in_kbs: 61522
    duplicate_bytes: 6285317
    warc_compressed_bytes: 11847465
    doc_rate: 6.86
    kb_rate: 418.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 May 18
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 May 25
    crawl: 214481
    start_date: 2016-05-25T13:56:29Z
    original_start_date: 2016-05-25T13:56:29Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-05-25T14:07:15Z
    end_date: 2016-05-25T13:58:59Z
    elapsed_ms: 146702
    discovered_count: 2970
    novel_count: 660
    duplicate_count: 355
    queued_count: 1955
    downloaded_count: 1015
    warc_revisit_count: 355
    warc_url_count: 1005
    total_data_in_kbs: 60280
    duplicate_bytes: 7583749
    warc_compressed_bytes: 11000106
    doc_rate: 6.92
    kb_rate: 410.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 May 25
  - Albany Student Press UAlbanys independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 May 26
  - Albany Student Press UAlbanys independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 May 28
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 June 1
    crawl: 215813
    start_date: 2016-06-01T13:56:28Z
    original_start_date: 2016-06-01T13:56:28Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-06-01T14:22:20Z
    end_date: 2016-06-01T14:11:38Z
    elapsed_ms: 866175
    discovered_count: 3827
    novel_count: 506
    duplicate_count: 499
    queued_count: 2822
    warc_revisit_count: 499
    warc_url_count: 988
    total_data_in_kbs: 44956
    duplicate_bytes: 18362706
    warc_compressed_bytes: 6823348
    doc_rate: 1.16
    kb_rate: 51.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 June 1
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 June 1
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 June 1
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 June 1
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 June 1
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 June 8
    crawl: 217591
    start_date: 2016-06-08T13:56:29Z
    original_start_date: 2016-06-08T13:56:29Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-06-08T14:12:38Z
    end_date: 2016-06-08T13:58:59Z
    elapsed_ms: 138098
    discovered_count: 3835
    novel_count: 501
    duplicate_count: 516
    queued_count: 2818
    downloaded_count: 1017
    warc_revisit_count: 516
    total_data_in_kbs: 44914
    duplicate_bytes: 17642458
    warc_compressed_bytes: 6830229
    doc_rate: 7.36
    kb_rate: 325.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 June 8
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 June 8
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 June 8
  - Albany Student Press UAlbanys independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 June 9
  - Albany Student Press UAlbanys independent, student-run weekly newspaper, 2016 June 10
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2016 June 15
    Meta tag for description: UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper
    crawl: 219430
    start_date: 2016-06-15T13:56:36Z
    original_start_date: 2016-06-15T13:56:36Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-06-15T14:08:38Z
    end_date: 2016-06-15T14:00:16Z
    elapsed_ms: 192849
    discovered_count: 3716
    novel_count: 558
    duplicate_count: 449
    queued_count: 2709
    warc_revisit_count: 449
    total_data_in_kbs: 46877
    duplicate_bytes: 19298173
    warc_compressed_bytes: 7021151
    doc_rate: 5.22
    kb_rate: 243.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2016 June 15
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2016 June 22
    crawl: 220976
    start_date: 2016-06-22T13:56:32Z
    original_start_date: 2016-06-22T13:56:32Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-06-22T14:08:00Z
    end_date: 2016-06-22T13:59:32Z
    elapsed_ms: 165833
    discovered_count: 3758
    novel_count: 559
    duplicate_count: 458
    queued_count: 2741
    warc_revisit_count: 458
    total_data_in_kbs: 44732
    duplicate_bytes: 22134389
    warc_compressed_bytes: 7210575
    doc_rate: 6.13
    kb_rate: 269.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2016 June 22
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2016 June 22